You had $107,000, you went to get to $1,000,000?
$150,000.
$150,000, excuse me.
What do you sell?
I sell content.
I grew up with social media,
and I technically use my age as a leverage to what I sell.
And now you're just gonna be a middle young white guy?
Yeah.
People don't trust necessarily older people in my business.
You're still young.
Yes, but when I hire someone like a new shooter
or a director of operations who's 25 and above,
they don't necessarily.
Oh, full folks, yeah.
Yeah, they don't necessarily.
So, but what are you saying though?
It's more of a trust issue with clientele.
I think this is like totally in your head, man.
Really?
Yeah, 100%.
You care, no one else cares.
People will care about your age
for the two seconds before you open your mouth.
That's like the absolute thinnest surface level judgment
that someone will make.
And then as soon as you open your mouth, no one cares.
People just care about how good you are.
So you just have to demonstrate expertise.